<!--
  ~ Copyright (c) 2009-2011. Created by serso aka se.solovyev.
  ~ For more information, please, contact se.solovyev@gmail.com
  ~ or visit http://se.solovyev.org
  -->

<resources>

	<string name="c_faq">FAQ</string>
	<string name="c_hints">Hints</string>
	<string name="c_screens">Screens</string>

	<string name="c_faq_content" formatted="false">
		<b>How can I remove the ads?</b>\n
		\n
		You can do it by purchasing the special option in the main application preferences.\n
		Purchase is done with Google Play and is linked to your google account.\n
		All your devices where same google account is set will be aware of purchase and will not show the
		advertisement.\n
		\n
		<b>Why Calculator++ needs INTERNET permission?</b>\n
		\n
		Currently application needs such permission only for one purpose - to show ads. If you buy the special option
		C++ will never use your internet connection.\n
		\n
		<b>How can I use functions written in the top right and bottom right corners of the button?</b>\n
		\n
		Push the button and slide lightly up or down. Depending on value showed on the button action will occur.\n
		\n
		<b>How can I toggle between radians and degrees?</b>\n
		\n
		To toggle between different angle units you can either change appropriate option in application settings\n or
		use the toggle switch located on the 6 button\n
		(current value is lighted with yellow color).\n
		Also you can use deg() and rad() functions and ° operator to convert degrees to radians and vice versa.\n
		\n
		<b>Examples:</b>\n
		268° = 4.67748\n
		30.21° = 0.52726\n
		rad(30, 21, 0) = 0.52971\n
		deg(4.67748) = 268\n
		\n
		<b>Does C++ support %?</b>\n
		\n
		Yes, % function can be found in the top right corner of / button.\n
		\n
		<b>Examples:</b>\n
		\n
		100 + 50% = 150\n
		100 * 50% = 50\n
		100 + 100 * 50% * 50% = 125\n
		100 + (100 * 50% * (25 + 25)% + 100%) = 150\n
		\n
		<b>Note:</b>\n
		\n
		100 + (20 + 20)% = 140,
		<b>but</b>
		100+ (20% + 20%) = 124.0\n
		100 + 50% ^ 2 = 2600,
		<b>but</b>
		100 + 50 ^ 2% = 101.08\n
		\n
		<b>Does C++ support fractional calculations?</b>\n
		\n
		Yes, you can type your fractional expression in the editor and use ≡ (in the top right corner of = button). Also
		you can use ≡ to simplify expression.\n
		\n
		<b>Examples:</b>\n
		\n
		2/3 + 5/9 ≡ 11/9\n
		2/9 + 3/123 ≡ 91/369\n
		(6 - t) ^ 3 ≡ 216 - 108t + 18t ^ 2 - t ^ 3\n
		\n
		<b>Does C++ support complex calculations?</b>\n
		\n
		Yes, just enter complex expression (using i or √(-1) as imaginary number).\n
		\n
		<b>Examples:</b>\n
		\n
		(2i + 1) ^ 2 = -3 + 4i\n
		e ^ i = 0.5403 + 0.84147i\n
		\n
		<b>Can C++ plot graph of the function?</b>\n
		\n
		Yes, type expression which contains 1 undefined variable (e.g. cos(t) and t has no value) and click on the
		result. In the context menu choose \'Plot graph\'.\n
		\n
		<b>Does C++ support matrix calculations?</b>\n
		\n
		No, it doesn\'t.\n
		\n
		<b>Why I\'ve got 1.76732452452345E-17 instead of 0?</b>\n
		\n
		Check the \'Round result\' preference in application settings - it should be turned on.\n
	</string>

	<string name="c_hints_content">
		1. You can omit unnecessary multiplication signs (instead of 3*t or t*sin(π*t) just type 3t or tsin(πt))\n\n
		2. Use ≡ (in the top right corner of = button) to simplify expression\n\n
		3. Just click on the result to copy it to the clipboard\n\n
		4. Use = button seldom - result is calculating on the fly\n\n
		5. Add constants for often used values (you can even save expressions)\n\n
		6. Use variables located on 4 and 5 buttons\n\n
	</string>

	<string name="c_screens_content">
		1.
		<b>Main screen:</b>
		is shown on application start, can be reached from another screen by pressing Back button.\n\n
		2.
		<b>Variables and Constants screen:</b>
		contains list of available constants. User may add some constants and variables here by clicking Add button.
		Short click on variable/constant inserts it into the editor, long click - opens variable editor window. Can be
		reached from the main screen by pressing π,… button.\n\n
		3.
		<b>Functions screen:</b>
		contains list of all available functions. Short click on function inserts it into the editor. Can be reached
		from the main screen by pressing f(x) button.\n\n
		4.
		<b>Operators screen:</b>
		contains list of all available operators. Short click on operator inserts it into the editor. Can be reached
		from the main screen by pressing ∂,… button.\n\n
		5.
		<b>History screen:</b>
		contains list of all actions done by user. Short click on history item sets it into the editor. Can be reached
		from the main screen by pressing M button.\n\n
		6.
		<b>Settings screen:</b>
		contains application preferences. Can be reached from the main screen by pressing Settings in menu.
	</string>

</resources>